哇 你玩得真好
Wow, you're really good at this.
大概是因为我重心比较低吧
Well, I have an extremely low center of gravity.
我的体型和金字塔差不多
I'm like a pyramid.
你怎么样了?
How you doing over there?
哦 但愿只是扭伤
Oh, I hope it's just a sprain.
我可不想再因为玩体感游戏
I cannot walk into that E.R.
而受伤去看急诊了
with another video game injury.
嘿 Sheldon 你要不要接我后面?
Hey, Sheldon, you want to play next?
我倒是想玩 不过我该走了
Oh, I would, but I'm on my way out.
- 去哪?  - 德州
- Where?  - Texas.
现在就走?
Right now?
为什么啊?
Why?
- 家里出事了?  - 是啊
- Is someone sick?  - Yes.
我姐姐的子宫里有了个婴儿
My sister's uterus came down with a baby.
哦 她怀孕了? 这是好事啊
Oh, she's pregnant? That's great.
你就要当舅舅了... Sheldon舅舅
You're gonna be an uncle... Uncle Sheldon.
不 应该是Cooper博士舅舅
No, I will be Uncle Dr. Cooper.
你怎么从来没说过她怀孕了?
How come you never said she was pregnant?
我还没告诉过你我哥哥有肾结石呢
Well, I never told you about my brother's kidney stone.
你想听听我家人的生殖器里
You want to hear about everything
还会掉出来什么东西吗?
that comes out of my family's genitals?
好吧 祝贺你啊
Well, congrats, and it's nice
- 而且你回去陪在你姐姐身边也很好啊  - 是啊
- you're gonna be there for your sister.  - Yes.
我是回去代替我姐夫的
I'm filling in for her husband who's recovering
他刚出了车祸 还在康复中
from a horrible motorcycle accident.
算他走运
Lucky duck.
哇 那你要去多久?
Wow, so, how long will you be gone?
她的预产期是明天
Well, she's due tomorrow.
不过她花了六年才上完高中
Although it did take her six years to finish high school,
所以 谁知道呢?
so who knows?
用我开车送你去机场吗?
Can I give you a ride to the airport?
哦 不用 谢了 真的不用麻烦了
Oh, no, thank you, I don't want to be an inconvenience.
快点快点 Leonard
Chop-chop, Leonard.
十分钟之内出发
We leave in ten minutes.
* 宇宙一度又烫又稠密 *
* Our whole universe was in a hot, dense state *
* 140亿年前终于爆了炸... 等着瞧! *
* Then nearly 14 billion years ago expansion started... Wait! *
* 地球开始降温 *
* The Earth began to cool *
* 自养生物来起哄 穴居人发明工具 *
* The autotrophs began to drool, Neanderthals developed tools *
* 我们建长城 我们建金字塔 *
* We built the Wall We built the pyramids *
* 数学 自然科学 历史 揭开神秘 *
* Math, Science, History, unraveling the mystery *
* 一切由大爆炸开始 *
* That all started with a big bang *
生活大爆炸 第七季十一集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调：初见
时间轴：pisces夜
翻译：酥酥final要爆炸 嗨森影 千欲吧 初见
校对：uu解放啦
好了好了 是这样的
All right, here's the deal.
Sheldon今年不在这里了 所以再也没有什么
Sheldon is gone, so the tree decorating rules
装饰圣诞树的规则了
are out the window.
是啊 也就是说
Yeah, which means
我们可以不用这个奇葩的
we don't have to use his ridiculous
装饰间距模板了
ornament-spacing template.
(一个致力于支持创新的网站)
而且我还要向大家宣布 这东西在Kickstarter网上
And I'm happy to report its kickstarter campaign
- 还没有拿到一分钱的投资  - 哦
- is holding strong at zero dollars.  - Ah.
等下 也就是说"星际迷航"和"星球大战"里的人物
Wait, so Star Wars and Star Trek characters
可以摆在同一个树枝上了?
can go on the same branch?
我知道 太神奇了
I know, it's crazy.
准备好狂欢吧 小伙伴们!
Welcome to the Thunderdome, people!
我以前从没这么干过
I've never done this before.
太有意思了
It's kind of fun.
是啊 要是你妈妈能看到
Yeah, if your mom could see
他的犹太小男孩现在的样子
her little Bar Mitzvah boy right now,
她一定会心脏病发作的
she'd have a heart attack.
说得对 我要拍张照片
Good idea, I'll take a picture.
亲爱的 我今年手头有点紧
Honey, I'm a little strapped for cash this year,
所以今年圣诞节我想送给你...
so for Christmas I was thinking of giving you...
这个
this.
爱死你了
I love it.
好啊
Okay.
不过你去年送我的也是这个
But it is what you got me last year.
- 好像是  - 还有昨晚也一样
- Yeah.  - And last night.
嗨
Hello.
嗨 Stuart
Hi, Stuart.
哦 真高兴你们没有等我来
Oh, good, I'm glad you guys
就开始了
didn't wait for me to start.
虽然你们说让我七点来
Although you said 7:00
而现在就是七点 不过无所谓啦
and it's... it's 7:00, but that's fine.
哦 估计是Sheldon
Oh, it's probably Sheldon.
嗨 Sheldon
Hi, Sheldon.
大家都在呢 打个招呼吧
Everybody's here, say hi.
- 嘿  - 嘿  - 嘿 伙计
- Hey.  - Hey.  - Hey, buddy.
- 你好啊  - 嗨
- Howdy.  - Hi.
嗨
Hello.
我一走
The second I go out of town
你们就办了个圣诞节派对?
you throw a Christmas party without me?
算是吧
Yeah, kind of.
这简直太贴心了
That's so thoughtful.
你们最懂我了
You guys are the best.
嘿 你姐姐怎么样?
Hey, how's your sister?
她一个小时之前开始阵痛了
She went into labor an hour ago.
不错啊 那你现在在医院?
That's wonderful. So you're at the hospital?
没有 她要在家里生孩子... 因为她想活在石器时代
No, she chose to have a home birth... because she wants
但是我们找不到山洞
to live in the Stone Age and a cave wasn't available.
其实很多人都觉得
You know, many people believe
在家生孩子更好 因为母亲处在一个
that home births are better because the mother
温暖舒适的环境当中
is in a warm, comfortable environment
而且身边照顾她的都是爱她的人
where she can be nurtured by loved ones.
还会把卧室的地板上
And turn the bedroom floor
弄得全都是羊膜
into an amniotic Slip 'n Slide.
Shelly 过来!
Shelly, come on!
你姐姐的羊水破了
Your sister's fully dilated
她想在血流成河之前
and she wants a nice family picture
和家人照一张合影!
before there's blood everywhere!
天啊
Oh, boy.
今天就不该穿我最爱的这件机器人的T恤
I picked the wrong day to wear my good robot T-shirt.
要是你怀了Sheldon的孩子
If you were having Sheldon's baby
你生孩子的时候想要他在屋里吗?
would you really want him in the room?
得了吧 如果她受孕的时候Sheldon在屋里
Yeah, if he's in the room when they're making the baby,
我就给你十美刀
I'll give you ten dollars.
嘿 我带了“生活多美好”那个电影过来
Hey, I brought over It's a Wonderful Life
你们一会要不要看
if you guys want to watch it later.
我喜欢那电影
Oh, I love that movie.
我没看过
I've never seen it.
- 我也没有  - 那电影很棒
- Me neither.  - It's great.
正值圣诞时节 Jimmy Stewart非常郁闷
It's Christmastime and Jimmy Stewart's really depressed
所以他决定跳桥自杀...
and he's gonna jump off a bridge and kill himself...
那不用看了 感同身受
Don't need to see it. Living it.
但之后 他看到了从未有他
But then he gets to see what the world
出生过的世界是怎样的
would be like if he'd never been born.
你能想象那是什么样吗?
Hey, you ever imagine what that would be like?
自己从未出生过?
Not being born?
你觉得呢?
What do you think?
你们嘲笑Sheldon
You make jokes about Sheldon,
但要不是因为他
but if it weren't for him,
我觉得我们大家
I don't think any of us
现在就不会聚在这儿了
would be sitting in this room right now.
真的? 就是因为Sheldon不在
Really? Sheldon not being here
我才会来这儿的
is the main reason I'm in this room.
我是说真的
It's true.
你们都不会认识我
None of you would know me.
你不会认识Bernadette
You wouldn't know Bernadette.
- 你也不会和Penny谈恋爱  - 这谁都说不准
- You wouldn't be dating Penny.  - You don't know that.
我去芝士蛋糕工厂很多年了
I've been going to the Cheesecake Factory for years.
也能认识她
I could have picked her up.
原来你不是开玩笑的
Oh, you weren't joking.
不是
No.
好吧 宝贝 我来告诉你
Okay, sweetie, let me tell you
事情会怎样进展
exactly how that would have gone down.
我决定了 我要约她出去
I'm gonna do it. I'm gonna ask her out.
我要从乳头挤出巧克力牛奶
I'm gonna squirt chocolate milk out of my nipples.
抱歉 我以为我们在说
Sorry, I thought we're saying things
不可能发生的事情
that are never gonna happen.
也许这次他真的会做
Maybe this time he's going to do it.
希望你们渴了 我挤
Hope you're thirsty, here it comes.
等着瞧
Watch me.
嘿 你们打算点单 还是需要再看看?
Hey, you guys ready to order or you need a few minutes?
我 呃 啊 嗯 我...
I, uh, ah, um, I...
那就是还需要再看看
A few minutes it is.
你没邀她出去 但也算发了很多声音
You didn't ask her out, but that was a lot of sounds.
你们弄得我太紧张了
You guys are making me nervous.
好吧 那你就自己过去跟她说
Fine, then go talk to her on your own.
我去了
I will.
抱歉
Excuse me.
什么事?
Yeah?
嗨 我叫Leonard?
Hi, uh, um, I'm Leonard?
真的? 感觉你自己都不确定
Really? You don't sound so sure.
不 我就是他
No, I am he.
好... 好吧
Uh, any... anyway, um,
我其实一直都想要
there's been something I've wanted to ask you
问你个问题 呃...
for a long time. Um...
- 什么问题?  - 好吧
- What's that?  - Eh, uh, well,
我在想... 如果你不忙...
I was wondering... if you're not too busy...
如果
um, uh, if,
如果你有兴趣...
if you'd be interested in...
能不能告诉我厕所在哪儿?
telling me where the restroom is?
我觉得你问得太晚了
I think you're too late.
得了吧 我可不会尿裤子
Come on, I would not have peed my pants.
- 她真厉害  - 说得太对了
- She nailed it.  - Sounds about right.
但你忘了 现实生活中我成功邀你出去了
But, you forget, I did ask you out in real life.
如果不是因为有Sheldon 你碰巧就住在
Which couldn't have happened if you didn't live across the hall
她对面的房间 你也就不会成功了
from her, which couldn't have happened without Sheldon.
你们也是一样
Same goes with you guys.
如果Leonard没跟Penny在一起
If Leonard wasn't with Penny,
她就不会撮合你们俩
she never would have set you up.
无所谓 Bernadette还是会去
Doesn't matter. Bernadette still would've been working
芝士蛋糕工厂上班
at the Cheesecake Factory,
我也还是会努力练肌肉蛋糕工厂的
and I still would've been working this beefcake factory.
你肯定会爱死我的
You would've been all over me.
这个嘛...
Well...
嘿 Penny 那桌能交给我吗?
Hey, Penny, can I take that table?
当然 怎么了?
Sure, why?
那个短脖子的家伙很可爱
The one in the turtleneck is cute.
张大嘴
Open wide,
一大勺好吃的驾到
here comes the happy train.
嗯 嚼啊嚼 真美味
Mm-hmm, chug-a chug-a, yum, yum.
噢
Oh.
等等
Hang on.
你嘴边... 有点东西
You got a... you got a little something.
算了吧
Never mind.
天啊
Oh, man,
太有我们的风格了
that is so us.
好吧 也许我们俩不会在一起
You know, maybe you and I wouldn't be together,
但你自己也不会过得很好
but you wouldn't have done so great yourself.
- 为什么?  - 因为我知道
- Why?  - Because I know exactly
你最后会跟怎样的人在一起
the kind of guy you would've ended up with.
嘿 宝贝
Hey, babe.
嘿 你交了房租吗?
Hey. Did you remember to pay the rent?
我干了件更好的事 我买了这些魔法豆
Better. I used the money to buy these magic beans.
好吧 他可能是有点白痴 但至少
Hey, he may be an idiot, but at least
他不会尿裤子
he didn't pee himself.
等等 还有一段
Oh, hold on.
宝贝 我尿裤子了
Aw, babe, I peed myself.
我也是
Me, too.
剧终
The end.
嗨 Sheldon
Hi, Sheldon.
一切都好吗?
Everything okay?
一点都不好
No, it's not.
我看到了点东西
I've seen things.
姑娘的东西
Lady things.
听我说
Listen to me.
那东西平时不是那样的
That is not the way they usually look.
无所谓了
Doesn't matter.
制造新生儿真可怕
This is no way to make new humans.
人从人身体里出来
People coming out of people.
像是地下魔法表演
It's some kind of dirty magic show.
嘿 Sheldon Lee Cooper
Sheldon Lee Cooper.
你现在赶紧滚回来
You get back in this room right now.
带个拖把
Bring a mop.
听到了吗?
Did you hear that?
一个拖把
A mop.
我有两个博士学位 可还得
I have two PhDs yet somehow I'm the janitor
清理我姐的产道
of my sister's birth canal.
嘿 Sheldon给大家发了条邮件
Hey, Sheldon sent us all an e-mail.
"在德州祝你们节日快乐"
"Happy holidays from Texas."
还发了图片过来
And there's pictures.
哦不!
Aah!
别看图片 千万别看
Don't open them. Do not open them.
哦 别这样
Oh, come on.
生孩子很自然 很可爱...
Childbirth is a natural, beautiful...
就好像奶牛被锯成两半了
Oh, it's like someone sawed a cow in half.
我父亲是妇科医生 我想我能承受
My father's a gynecologist, I think I can handle it.
好吧 我成基佬了
And, now, I'm gay.
知道吗 我在想 如果没有Sheldon
You know, I was thinking. Without Sheldon,
我们也许就不会在一起
most of us would have never met,
但是Penny仍旧会是他们邻居
but Penny would still live across from him.
如果世上没有Leonard的话
And with Leonard out of the picture,
我们都知道会发生什么
we all know what that would mean.
知道吗?
We do?
嘿 Sheldon
Hey, Sheldon.
你好
Hello.
搓衣服?
Doing laundry?
当然我在搓衣服
Of course I'm doing laundry.
星期六是挫衣日
Saturday night is laundry night,
而且我在洗衣房 那么...
and I'm in a laundry room, so...
所以你的推理没错
I believe your inference is justified.
哦 好吧 我猜的不错
Oh, my inference is justified.
Sheldon 你真幽默
Sheldon, you are so funny.
总之 我也要搓我的衣服
Anyway, I need to do my laundry, too,
因为我的衣服很想被洗个遍
because these clothes are so dirty.
就好像穿着衣服的我也想被洗一下
Almost as dirty as the dirty girl who's wearing them.
好了 别意淫了
Okay, that's enough.
- 不同意  - 继续
- Disagree.  - Keep going. More.
怎么样?
So, what do you think?
两边有点不对称 不过没啥大问题
A tad asymmetrical, but nothing to be concerned about.
求求你了 Sheldon 我需要你
Please, Sheldon. I need you.
要我... 干嘛?
To... what?
带我
To take me.
你不把衣服穿上 我哪儿也不带你去
I'm not taking you anywhere till you put on a shirt.
来吧 Sheldon 你和我 就在这儿
Come on, Sheldon. You and me right here.
Penny 我和你说了一千遍
Penny, for the thousandth time,
我会一直为某人守身如玉
I'm saving myself for someone special.
也许是一位可爱的神经科眼镜妹
Perhaps a cute bespectacled neuroscientist
有着土黄色的头发
with hair the color of mud.
我知道我该怎么做了
I think I know how to change your mind.
够了吧
That's enough.
我还可以接受
I was okay with it.
那边如何了 Sheldon?
How's it going, Sheldon?
情况好多了
Actually, much better.
那好啊 孩子生下来了吗?
Oh, good. Is the baby born yet?
我不清楚 我才回房间里
I don't know. I just got back.
那你去哪儿了?
Where'd you go?
我老妈说让我去拿点毛巾
My mother asked me to get some towels.
听了她的模糊要求 我就小小利用了一下
I took advantage of the vague request
跑去毛巾店里逛了一圈
and went to Bed, Bath & Beyond.
小点声! 我在打电话!
Excuse me! I'm on the phone!
真没礼貌
So rude.
还有一条 Penny
Here's another one. Penny,
如果不是Sheldon
if it weren't for Sheldon,
(蜘蛛侠 神奇四侠 X战警 绿巨人的作家)
你就不会知道著名漫画作家 斯坦李
you never would have met comic book legend Stan Lee.
太好了
Great.
至少Leonard
At least Leonard,
我和Howard还会是好朋友的
Howard and I would have always been friends.
那为什么你们三个没住在一起?
Hey, how come you three never got an apartment together?
我们谈过这事的 但是Howard
We talked about it, but Howard was in
和他老妈互相离不开啊
a pretty serious relationship with his mom.
我和她一起住是为了省钱
I lived with her to save money.
对啊 你不用买啥吃的了
Yeah, you didn't have to buy groceries
因为你可以享受母乳
'cause you were breast-feeding.
我想如果不是我的话
Aw, so I guess if it weren't for me,
你还会和你老妈住一起?
you'd still be living with her, huh?
不一定
Not exactly.
什么叫"不一定"?
What do you mean, "not exactly"?
当然 情况肯定不一样了
Well, things would be a little different.
Howard 我午饭在哪儿?!
Howard, where's my lunch?!
我饿死了!
I'm starving!
我知道你很饿
I know you're starving.
邻居都知道你很饿
The neighbors know you're starving.
就连非洲饥民都知道你很饿!
There's starving people in Africa who know you're starving!
就这点?! 食物不够啊!
That's it?! There's not enough food!
你都把地球都扫遍了! 我不知道给你喂啥了!
Well, you cleaned out Earth! I don't know what else to do!
你还不是和你妈妈住一起?
How is this any different?
你还没让我说完
You didn't let me finish.
给你吧 老妈
Here you go, Mother.
你真是个好孩子 Howard!
You're a good boy, Howard!
你真是好孩子!
Such a good boy!
等下... 是她自己死了还是你杀的?
Wait... did she die or did you kill her?
西红柿还是番茄 她死了不就行了
Eh, tomato, tomato. The important thing is she's dead.
那你俩为啥没住在一起?
Hey, so how come you two didn't move in together?
他想要私人空间
This guy wanted a place of his own
因为他以为他一定能成为万人迷
because he was sure he was gonna be a ladies' man.
是啊 但我错了
Yeah, I was wrong.
但如果我们住一起 那咱也会很愉快的
But I do think you and I would have had a great time.
来吧 Leonard 晚饭好了
Come on, Leonard, dinner.
来了
Coming.
等下
Hang on.
为啥我这么胖?
Why would I be fat?
因为没有女朋友要看你裸体
You'd have no girlfriend to see you naked,
所以你空虚得只剩下吃了
you'd try to fill the void with food,
而我可是曾经做过油炸煎饼的人
and I'm an enabler who once deep-fried a pancake.
为啥你不胖呢?
Why can't you be fat, too?
你甜点想要啥?
What do you want to do for dessert?
早上还剩下半个蛋糕
I think there's still half a cake from breakfast.
已经没了
No, there's not.
嘿 小伙伴们
Hey, guys.
- Stuart  - Stuart啊
- Stuart.  - Stuart.
你在干嘛?
What are you doing?
我...
I...
只是想参与到你们的故事里
just wanted to be in anyone's story.
但你为什么变胖?
Yeah, but why are you fat?
因为Leonard很胖
'Cause Leonard was fat.
Amy 那你呢?
Amy, what about you?
如果没和Sheldon在一起 你觉得你会怎样?
What do you think you'd be doing if you never met Sheldon?
我说不好
It's hard to say,
也许我的生活... 完全不同
my life would be so... different.
你可以说"活得更好" Sheldon又听不见
You can say "better." Sheldon can't hear you.
我不知道
I don't know.
# 祝我生日快乐 #
# Happy birthday to me #
# 泪水滴蛋糕上了 #
# There's tears in the frosting #
# 祝我生日快乐 #
# Happy birthday to me. #
人家不说了行了吧
I'll stop now.
怎么样了 Sheldon?
How's it going, Sheldon?
生了
That's it.
宝宝就在旁边
The baby's here.
是男孩
It's a boy.
- 恭喜  - 耶
- Congrats.  - Aw. Yay.
太感谢了
Oh, thank you.
我真怕自己做不到
I wasn't sure I was gonna to make it.
我妈给我买了刨冰
But my mother gave me some ice chips,
我姐告诉我要保持呼吸
my sister told me to breathe.
我不停地对自己说 "Sheldon
And I just thought to myself, "Sheldon,
"绿灯侠电影你都能忍
"if you can make it through the Green Lantern movie,
这次你一定行的"
you can make it through this."
你真棒 哥们
Well, good for you, buddy.
快回去吧
We'll let you get back in there.
哦 不 我可不想再去了
Oh no, no, I'm not going back in there.
新生儿真是太闹腾了
That baby is so irritating.
从出生到现在哭个不停
Has literally been crying his entire life.
哦 他已经继承了谢耳朵叔叔的衣钵了
Aw, he's already taking after Uncle Shelly.
快去吧 Sheldon 你应该过去
Come on, Sheldon, you should go.
为什么?
Why?
你总是抱怨在你成长的过程中
Well, you always complain that you never
没有一个充满智慧的榜样
had an intelligent role model growing up,
你现在可以为你的侄子做一个这样的榜样
and now you can be one for your nephew.
啊 好吧 我过去
Ugh, all right, I'll go.
但现在看来 他的集中注意力
But from what I've seen, his attention span
和膀胱控制能力一样糟糕
is as limited as his bladder control.
你真的说服他了
You actually got him to do it.
嗯 你总是说
Yeah, you keep saying
Sheldon对我们影响很大
how much Sheldon has affected all of us,
但是你对他的影响力也很大
but you've clearly had an impact on him.
要是真像你说的
If that were true,
我也不会到现在还独居了
I wouldn't still be living alone.
好吧 也不是独居
Well, not exactly alone.
我还有一袋50磅的大米
I do have a 50 pound sack of rice
外面罩着Sheldon的衣服
with one of Sheldon's T-shirts on it.
说实话 Sheldon比你想象的更在乎你
I'm telling you, Sheldon cares for you more than you think.
我希望你说的是真的
I wish I could believe you.
也希望大米袋子里面没老鼠
I also wish there wasn't a mouse living in Rice Sheldon.
等一下 我要提前送你
Hang on, I'm gonna give you a little
一个小圣诞礼物
early Christmas present.
我要给你看看这个 但如果你告诉Sheldon
I'm gonna show you something, but if you ever told Sheldon
他这辈子都不会理我了
he'd probably never speak to me again.
所以快点去告诉他
So, if you want to tell him, that's fine.
看
Look.
我不懂
I don't understand.
他把你的照片设成了屏保
He made you his screensaver.
哦
Oh.
哇
Wow.
我都不知道
I had no idea.
他这么稀罕我
He is so into me.
等一下
Wait, wait,
我的照片呢?
where'd I go?
哦 第一张是你 然后是沼泽怪
Oh, well, it's you, Swamp Thing,
史蒂芬·霍金 蜘蛛侠...
Stephen Hawking, Spider-Man...
但最起码 你也入选了
but, look, you're in the mix.
我也入选了
I am in the mix.
还是里面身材最火辣的
And I'm the hottest one.
那是谁?
Who's that?
哦 是居里夫人
Oh, Madame Curie.
没关系 她已经去世了
That's fine, she's dead.
你没事吧?
You okay?
你回来我太高兴了
Just really glad you're back.
我也很高兴
Me, too.
我有好多电视剧要补回来
I got a lot of TV to catch up on.
我好想你
I missed you.
(星球大战里的角色)
韩·索罗说过 "我知道"
To quote Han Solo, "I know."
你想不想我?
Did you miss me?
我真希望你能陪我去
I would've preferred to have you there with me.
哦
Oh.
或者替我去
Or instead of me.
你抱小宝宝了吗?
Did you hold the baby?
抱了
I did.
那?
And?
有何感想?
How did it make you feel?
看着毯子里的小东西
Looking into the blank, innocent eyes
争着无辜的大眼睛
of a creature that couldn't begin to comprehend
理解不了我在说什么?
anything I was saying?
就和上班的时候一样
Basically just another day at the office.
我要上了
I'm gonna do it.
我要把她约出来
I'm gonna ask her out.
我的奶头能喷出巧克力牛奶
Yeah, and chocolate milk is gonna squirt out of my nipples.
不上就闭嘴 你挤我就喝
Put up or shut up. You make it, I'll drink it.
- 你们还需要点什么吗?  - 呃
- You guys need anything else?  - Uh,
需要你的电话号码外加一个芝士蛋糕
your phone number and one more cheesecake.
不好意思 我有男朋友了
I'm sorry, I have a boyfriend.
事实上 他已经来了
In fact, there he is now.
可以走了吗 亲爱的?
Ready to go, sweetheart?
不亲我一下我可不走
Not until I get my kiss.
生活大爆炸全体成员祝大家节日快乐!
生活大爆炸进入冬歇期 下一集将于1月3日回归
圣城家园字幕组祝大家圣诞快乐 期末顺利!
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调：初见
时间轴：pisces夜
翻译：酥酥final要爆炸 嗨森影 千欲吧 初见
校对：uu解放啦